Westfall, Marshall Collection of Audio-Visual Materials 6329 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Marshall Westfall Collection of Audio-Visual Materials
1981-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Westfall, Marshall
6329 AV
3.11 cubic feet
3.1 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
7513242
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 27, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6329 P: Marshall Westfall Collection of Photographs
7513242
- pt.1- Westfall Media Clips (Box 1.1)
- pt.2 - Westfall Media Clips (Box 1.2)
- From Westfall Master tape (Box 2)
- disc 1 - Westfall "Workers Against Concessions Rally" (disc 1-2) (Box 3.1)
- disc 2 - Westfall "Workers Against Concessions Rally" (disc 2-2) (Box 3.2)
- Mike Westfall on News Programs (Box 4)
- Stockholders' meeting 5-22-1987; "Roger and Me" deleted clips & scenes 1989 (Box 5)
- 1990 Cola Rally, Detroit, MI (Box 6)
- CERP: War o Survival Film 1981-1982; CERP 6-14-1984; Panel discussion 6-14-1984, 1981-1984 (Box 7)
- Phone Zone Radio Show [tape 1 of 3], 1987 (Box 8)
  Scope and Contents
  WTAC Flint, MI, Mike Westfall with Perry Wright. Auto issues, UAW, Plant Closings, Foreign sourcing, Corporate restructuring, Job loss, Concessions
- Phone Zone Radio Show [tape 2 of 3], 1987 (Box 9)
- Phone Zone Radio Show [tape 3 of 3], 1987 (Box 10)
- Flint Radio Dave Barber Show, 1987 (Box 11)
  March 30, 1987. Morning Magazine, Mike Westfall
- Talk To Me Radio Show, 1981 (Box 12)
  November 9, 1981. WXYZ, Detroit, Mi, Mike Westfall with David Newman. UAW ways of dealing with corporate restructured job loss.
- Flint Nightline Radio Show, 1987 (Box 13)
  WTRX, Flint, MI, Mike Westfall with Pete Clawson and Victor Reuther. Corporate restructuring, UAW concessions
- Flint Nightline Radio Show [tape 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 14)
  July 3, 1985. WTRX, Flint, MI, Mike Westfall with Perry Wright and Ralph Nader. GM taxes, Corporate restructuring, Job loss.
- Flint Nightline Radio Show [tape 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 15)
- NPR (National Public Radio), 1982 (Box 16)
  February 22, 1982. WFBE, Flint, MI, Mike Westfall (UAW National CERP Chairman) with Ken Cameron (GM Spokesman) and Gary Horn (UAW Local 659 CERP Chairman).
- Flint Nightline Radio Show [tape 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 17)
  May 20, 1987. WTRX, Flint, MI, Steve Clawson with Rosemary Holland and Tom Gilbert from the Mike Westfall Committee. Concessions, Corporate restructuring.
- Flint Nightline Radio Show [tape 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 18)
- NPR (National Public Radio), 1982 (Box 19)
  October 6, 1982. WFBE, Flint, MI, Worklife Special on Technology and Displacement. Karen Ror and Nancy Rosaver with Mike Westfall (Westfall Awareness Committee), Reggie Harris (GM Public Relations), and Tony Chifona (Genesee County Planning and Development.
- Flint Nightline Radio Show, 1985 (Box 20)
  October 9, 1985. WTRX, Flint, MI, Mike Westfall with Perry Wright and Jim Musselman (Ralph Nader staff). GM Property tax reduction.
- University of Michigan Panel Discussion on GM Property Tax, 1985 (Box 21)
  October 10, 1985. Flint, MI. Mike Westfall.
- Large, Media-Covered GM Property Tax Backyard Rally [tape 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 22)
  July 28, 1985. Conducted by Mike Westfall with guest, Ralph Nader.
- Large, Media-Covered GM Property Tax Backyard Rally [tape 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 23)
  July 28, 1985. Conducted by Mike Westfall with guest, Ralph Nader
- University of Michigan Panel Discussion on Job Loss Solutions [tape 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 24)
  June 17, 1984. Mike Westfall (National Westfall Awareness Committee), Dr. Robin Widgery (Prof. of Organizational Behavior, GMI), Dr. Frithjof Bergman (Head of Philosophy, U of M Ann Arbor), Dr. Richard Gull (Prof. of Philosophy, U of M Flint), and Dr. John Larson (Prof. of Management, U of M Flint).
- University of Michigan Panel Discussion on Job Loss Solutions [tape 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 25)
- Westfall Group Sponsored Anti-Concession Rally. Flint, MI., 1987 (Box 26)
  April 5, 1987. Mike Westfall with Dave Barber (Flint TV and Radio Personality).